hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jeremy
Krakowski and on this podcast I help
coaches trainers mentors speakers and
authors reach more people with their
message and make a whole heck of a lot
more money with their businesses so that
they can have more impact worldwide I've
been in this industry for over 20 years
helping authors and thought leaders
reach Millions with their messages and
make tens of millions of dollars on the
internet using strategies that are
proven
that have a formula that you can follow
and that consistently work and so if I'm
bringing these strategies to you it's
because they are tested and work and
they will work for you as well however
I'm not always going to say everything
that you want to hear I'm gonna
say things that will challenge your
belief systems oftentimes we'll go
against the quote-unquote Norms that
you've been taught
but that is what's going to make you a
lot of money and that is why most
coaches trainers and mentors fail in
their businesses because they're doing
everything that actually doesn't work
and oftentimes they're uncomfortable
doing the things that actually produce a
lot of money and so what I do is I don't
hold back anything I give you everything
from behind the curtain of what's
working from inside of our businesses
from inside of our testing
and I bring this to you because it works
and it's going to produce results for
you now here's what I want to talk about
is with your copywriting the number one
thing that most coaches
and this is after working with hundreds
of coaches and this is specifically in
the last year that we have seen is I can
teach you everything about copywriting
and offer creation and sales copy and
all that and yet
almost everybody gets this one wrong
and in fact you might have even heard me
Teach what I'm going to share today
and I'm going to teach it in a way that
I haven't taught before because I'm
going to get really specific on the one
thing that most people get wrong
most people are playing it too safe
timid
they're avoiding crossing the line
in one particular area when it comes to
their offer see when you want to attract
the right clients you're targeting is a
two-fold Formula okay
you have two elements that are just as
important as each other
don't ever let somebody convince you
that one is more important than the
other
you have the targeting of your paid
advertising if you're running paid ads
and this is
generally we will use a look-alike
audience for this but this could also be
a broad audience that you're using
initially look-alike audiences are going
to be much better than a more broad
audience
but your sales copy the words
that you say that you write that are
written on the page particularly your
headline
and the name of your offer and the
promise of your offer that people see
when they first click your ad when they
first click to a page where you're like
hey get this free download for me or get
this training or get this uh virtual
event or we're doing this three-day
virtual Mastermind or this six week
challenge or whatever it is there's one
element
that changes the game in all of this
and what it is is that most people get
wrong
is this one element is they are avoiding
everything but they're talking about
everything but a very specific outcome
or result let me explain what I mean by
that
is I could teach you how to publish
the best songs in the world
or I could teach you how to get your
music heard
or I could teach you how to win a Grammy
award
those are three very different outcomes
that are mentioned and you might say
well no if they make the best songs in
the world then it's just it's a
naturally occurring part of the process
that they will possibly win a Grammy but
I don't want to promise that and that's
your problem
is you are tiptoeing around most people
do this tiptoeing around
boldly expressing a dream outcome and
result
your goal and your mission
to make the kind of money that you want
to make is to promise the the biggest
dream
to your Target customers now they might
not all have that biggest dream
but everybody else whose dreams fit
inside that of making a Grammy award
making eight figures in their coaching
business
they will be attracted to your offer
because you're the one who is boldly
willing to say what everybody else is
too afraid of because they're afraid of
not working out
being wrong
being too too bold too out there was
what I say
I'm afraid of
what if I can't make that result happen
for everybody
I hear this all the time
what if I can't promise that outcome for
a hundred percent of everybody I'm sorry
but what Fantasyland do you ever think
that
you could produce that outcome for
anybody and that you only talk about
what you produce for everybody see
that's the mistake that coaches make and
this is where most people stop listening
to me because they believe that what I'm
about to teach is unethical according to
their belief systems they believe that
you should only ever talk about what you
can guarantee for 100 of everybody who
connects with you
so if I can't guarantee that 100 of
everybody who connects with me wins a
Grammy award then I better not say that
in my sales copy if I can't guarantee
that a hundred percent of all my clients
make six figures then I can't say that
I'm going to show you how to make six
figures I'm sorry that's a load of crap
and it's tied and connected to fear and
worry of what other people think about
you that's all it is
you're trying to play it safe to not
push the envelope
so that other people don't think ill of
you
and you're you're using your fear of
other people's opinions or maybe you
justify it as well I'm I'm I'm being
honest
I'm sorry
get off your Pious High Horse 100 hmm
start promising bold
out there outcomes that only the top
point one percent of your clients might
ever achieve
in all of our offers we call them how to
start a six-figure group coaching offer
how to create how to make six figures
with your paid advertising is every
single person who opts into a free
training with me about making six
figures with paid advertising going to
make six figures
no that is ridiculous to even have a
thought that that could possibly happen
and yet that is the standard of thinking
that most coaches go through and so then
they play it safe with their sales copy
and they avoid talking about the dream
outcome the greatest outcome the biggest
result the the the one that everybody
wants that's out there such as
win a Grammy award if you're teaching
somebody how to write great songs how to
get their music heard see this is how we
actually scaled Rick Pino's coaching to
over a million dollars a month is we
weren't afraid to make the Bold promise
that we're going to show you how to get
your music heard and walk you and hold
your hand all the way to the Grammys now
did every single person win a Grammy
that went through that no they didn't
however
the coaches that were part of the
program had won a Grammy they had
actually one Grammy Awards actually had
track record of that
and so if you have a track record of
being able to accomplish a certain
outcome and then you can help somebody
with that outcome that you want to
promise that outcome even if not
everybody reaches that outcome in your
sales copy
and this one thing
most coaches trainers and mentors avoid
because for whatever reason they have
made it up in their mind that they need
to play it safe back it off just a
little bit I can't promise everybody's
gonna make six figures so I'm gonna say
I'm just going to show you how to
make some money you know make an extra
100 bucks hmm
I don't want to push the envelope too
much and this is the cycle that coaches
mentors and trainers get in is tiptoeing
around and not actually saying the Bold
outcome that they could produce and then
they wonder why they aren't attracting
leads
why they're not getting people
registering for them
because of this need
to operate within a tiny little safe box
of what what feels comfortable
and so you're gonna have to stretch
yourself in your comfort zone when you
do this it's going to stretch your
comfort zone what is and this is what I
tell people
0.1 the top point one percent of people
that work with you in your coaching that
might go through a free training with
you a free training with you what
outcome might they get if they hired you
at the end of it and became a client and
followed that all the way to the end for
me it would be becoming an eight and
nine figure coach because that's what
we've helped people do
but if I'm not bold enough to actually
say that nobody's gonna know that and
I'm going to attract crappy people
in front of me I'm going to attract
people that are just not even worth my
time to talk to
I'm gonna attract people that will waste
my ad dollars
that will cost me a ton of money and you
might be saying well you know I don't I
don't speak in absolutes I don't speak
in outcomes like that I don't or here's
what I hear a lot of people say I hurt I
help such a wide range of people
and so
I can't pick just one outcome
one result yeah no you've convinced
yourself of that that's that's a lie
that you tell yourself to make you
feel better about the fact that you're
not doing this because I promise you
this maybe it's not one outcome but it's
a series of outcomes that could be
identified by a statement and so if we
look at what is the end goal that you
get people to in your business what is
that dream
that your clients would have or that
they can get to
and then how would you quantify that
to a hundred people for me I Quantified
in my business that I can help coaches
trainers and mentors scale their
businesses to make six seven and even
eight figures in sales
using strategies and techniques that are
proven and that work and guess what you
know what this one is actually one of
the top strategies
and what's crazy is this one strategy
right here I will work with people for
months and they will do everything else
but this
because this challenges their belief
about what they are capable of
as a coach this is going to challenge
your belief about your capabilities of
what results that you can produce but if
you've done it once you can do it again
you can do it again and you can do it
again and even if you're just learning
even if you're just a beginner
you know my mom when she created her
stocks portfolio program
she wasn't the biggest trainer or expert
Guru at stock trading but she knew how
to increase the portfolio and so she
promised to show people the best
strategies that would take them to build
their portfolio to fifty thousand
dollars
she had done it and she knew how to get
people there
and she was bold enough to declare and
say I can get you there
instead of playing it safe like you know
I'm going to show you some little
strategies that they might work for you
if you do everything like stop playing
it safe start being bold start going to
even the extreme level with the language
that you use when it comes to the
promises that you make and the
Declarations of what's possible when
working with you this is one of the
greatest reasons why I see people in
their coaching businesses fail
to make money
is they are
avoiding
mentioning the dream top point one
percent outcome
and so I want you to challenge this just
for yourself why are you avoiding
putting this in your sales copy
why are you avoiding putting this in
your offer
here's a question for you what are you
trying to avoid happening
if you did
are you trying to avoid people coming
back to you and saying well you promised
I would make a Grammy and now I didn't
so now I'm gonna sue you or hold you
accountable I'm gonna ask for all my
money back and I'm angry with you that
now I didn't get that result and you
promised
is that what you're wanting is that what
you're afraid of
you're trying to manage maintain and
control other people's choices listen we
don't want to lie to people and
guarantee these results that's the thing
you're not ever going to be able to
guarantee these results to anybody ever
but in your headline in your sales copy
you need to be bold with uh I'm gonna
show you how to go from where you are to
ultimate dream that very few people ever
will accomplish including you
and boldly Express that in your copy and
not tiptoe around or be afraid
of it not happening or or people getting
upset at you or it going wrong or
some of you just got
ego or critic self-criticism or
something up here telling you it's wrong
even to do that
there might be something inside your
head that tells you this is wrong
and I can't do that and I want you to
challenge that belief system straight up
if you want to be a success as a coach
trainer Mentor or speaker you need to
challenge that belief system
your clients are buying a result and an
outcome there is no reason anybody will
ever spend any money with you unless
they trust that that outcome that dream
is possible by working with you so how
are they ever going to even have that in
their mind that that's possible if you
don't say it
well I don't want to project those
dreams in their mind if they're too
grandios what in the world who taught
you to think that small
you have to start thinking bigger you
have to start dreaming big you have to
stop playing in the teeny tiny weensy
windy little sandbox of safety that
you've always been in and start pushing
the envelope and you will be amazed
the radical shift in the outcome that
happens for you I was talking with one
of my clients
she helps people write books with AI and
I said her sales copy said I'm going to
help you reach the ultimate success
by publishing your book and I said okay
let's get more specific I'm going to
show you how to get raving reviews on
Amazon and to sell out of your book
and I said did you get that yourself
absolutely then you have to promise that
outcome you have to tell the story
you have to you have to say the actual
thing that's gonna happen
and take that risk to put it out there
and this is what most coaches trainers
and mentors are avoiding because that's
just it's just fear or
if they say it's not fear it's uh it's
wisdom or it's I just don't say things
like that or it's it's just it's blow me
whatever it's Pride it's ego and it's
Gonna Keep You Broke
This is Gonna Make You the kind of money
that you want to make in your coaching
business and so if you want to make
eight figures as a coach
stop playing
start
declaring
writing saying speaking posting putting
on your headlines the Ultimate Dream
.01
outcome that just one person might get
if they join your training
but that's what you're marketing that is
the result that you're marketing that is
the result that you are promising to
people
without any hesitation
without any lack of belief
with total confidence
when you start making this shift
everything else in your marketing is
going to change
what you got to do see you still got a
choice to make I I will have a message
like this
a video like this and that's a powerful
video
99 of people who listen to what I just
said will ignore it you there's a just
because 99 well there was a massive
chance that you will ignore exactly what
I just said because you will have a
hundred and one thousand reasons why you
can't
until one day you finally realize the
truth
and when that day comes that's when
you'll start to make the kind of money
that you want to make or you can choose
now
stop
operating the way you always have
and to shift into what produces results
and to start doing this
and to start making the kind of money
you want to make
is it guaranteed that you're going to
make all the money you want to make
doing this absolutely not it's silly
it's silly
but this is going to get you as close as
possible
sales copy offers it's a test it's all a
test you can't avoid there's no it's a
non-negotiable that you will have to
experiment and try out different offers
that you will have to try things out
and listen you might have some sales
copy that sounds really good
but it might not convert in the
marketplace will tell you what converts
this is going to get you as close as
possible to that all right everybody
listen if you've listened to this check
out the other close to 200 podcast
episodes that we have
stay plugged in with us every single
week we have over a thousand videos on
YouTube
I host Live Events every single month
where I help you as a coach as a trainer
as a mentor scale your business and
start to make the kind of money that you
want to make
so stay plugged in with us as well get
on the waiting list for our coaching
program the client growth accelerator if
you're a coach trainer Mentor speaker or
author and you want to make a massive
amount of impact and a massive amount of
cash flow in your business that's what
this program is for
we'll talk soon everybody have a good
one